

# Caia juré

## UX/UI & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

## SKILLS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Indesign

Sketch

InvisionApp

Principle

HTML/CSS

**JavaScript** 

## LANGUAGES

CATALAN

Native

Native

ENGLISH

Intermediate

## CONTACT

FMAIL

laiajuve@hotmail.com

PHONE

+34 617 158 722

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/ laia-juvé-navarro-432b17116/

## ABOUT ME

I am studying at Ironhack in Barcelona learning UX/UI Design.

I am 26 years old . I have four years of work experience in various Graphic Designer projects. I'm a very passionate designer that's always wanting to grow, learn and try something new.

I love to travel, the fashion and new technologies.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Ironhack

Part Time UX/UI Design | Bootcamp 05/2018

#### Elisava

Degree in Design | 09/2010 - 05/2015

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Graphic Designer Freelance - AÜA**

11/2017 - Now | Barcelona-Andorra

- Style Manuals
- Branding
- Graphic design advertising
- Packaging Design

## **Graphic Designer - The Dream VR**

05/2016 - Now | Barcelona

- Branding
- Style Manuals
- Digital Graphic Design
- Document Layout
- Image Processing

# **Graphic & Interior Designer - Manuel Torres Design**

11/2014 - 04/2016 | Barcelona

- Branding
- Online Creatives
- Image Processing
- Trend Reports